Rosa Parks Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Oversize, 1900-2006 (Box OV 1 -OV 17)
  - Books Owned by Parks (Box OV 17)
    - Holy Bible
      - C. H. Robinson and Co., with a register of family births, marriages, and deaths, 1900 (Container 34) See also Container 2, Copies of family register pages